[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：作用域是编程中最重要的发明之一。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Scope is one of the most important inventions in programming.
我们从Algol 60得到的
We got it from ALGOL 60.
几乎所有现代语言都有块范围，JavaScript没有。
Almost all modern languages have block scope, JavaScript doesn't.
JavaScript只有函数作用域，这证明它并不是一件坏事。
JavaScript only has functions scope, which turns out it's not a bad thing.
这个函数范围足以编写好的程序。
That function scope is sufficient for writing good programs.
问题是大多数用JavaScript编写的程序员都是经过培训的
The problem is that most programmers who are writing in JavaScript were trained
在Java或C或其他C-ish语言中，并期望具有块范围。
in Java or C or other C-ish languages, and expected to have block scope.
并且关于声明变量的位置的规则在块范围内是不同的
And the rules about where you declare variables are different in block scope
语言与函数范围语言。
languages versus function scope languages.
而这种困惑可能会导致错误。
And that confusion can cause errors.
这是因为var语句工作的疯狂方式。
And this is because of the crazy way that the var statement works.
今天下午我们将更多地关注var。
We'll look more at var this afternoon.
因此，由于这种疯狂，我建议在顶部声明所有变量
So because of this craziness, I recommend declare all of your variables at the top
函数，因为JavaScript实际上将在那里声明它们。
of the function because that is where JavaScript actually will declare them.
所以如果你把你的声明放在那里，那就增加了谁是
And so if you put your declarations there, that increases the likelihood that who is
只要阅读过你的程序，你就会正确地理解这个程序是什么
ever reading your program will correctly understand what the program is
正在做。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我找到了这个地方
doing. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I find the place
让人们最困惑的是for的归纳变量
that gets people the most confused is in the induction variable of the for
声明。
statement.
他们真的很想拯救我们的我在那里。
They really want to save our I there.
我建议不要，甚至不要在那里做。
And I recommend no, don't even do it there.
将条形图i移动到函数的顶部。
Move the bar I to the top of the function.
他们真的很生气，他们开始尖叫，他们说，但是
And they get really upset, and they start screaming and they say, but
用Java不是这样写的。
that's not how you write it in Java.
我说，用你正在写的语言写。
And I say, write in the language you're writing in.
Java是一种不同的语言。
That Java is a different language.
他们看起来很相似，但是
They look similar but
这是一种不同的语言，有一套不同的坏部分。
it's a different language with a different set of bad parts.
在JavaScript中，您不想这样做，因为它
In JavaScript, you don't wanna be doing that because it
不会像你想象的那样。
doesn't do what you imagine it does.
在ECMA大会今年6月发表的EX6中。
In EX6, which was published in June of this year by the ECMA General Assembly.
现在JavaScript中有一个let语句，它现在开始找到它的
There's now a let statement in JavaScript which is now starting to find its
实现的方式，当它变得完全无处不在时，我将
way into implementations and when that becomes totally ubiquitous, I will
建议停止使用var，从现在开始使用let，因为let将尊重块范围。
recommend stop using var, use let from now on because let will respect block scope.
除非您的代码必须在IE 6上运行，因为let是IE 6上的语法错误，并且
Unless your code has to run on IE 6 because let is a syntax error on IE 6 and
您的代码将永远不会在IE7或IE8或
your code won't ever run or in IE 7 or on IE 8 or
IE 9或IE 10或IE 11，但如果您必须在Edge 2或
IE 9 or IE 10 or IE 11, but if you have to run on Edge 2 or
不管下一个叫什么。
whatever the next one is gonna be called.
是啊。
Yeah.
让。否则
Let. Otherwise,
继续使用var。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]当前
keep using var. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH] Does the current
边缘允许让？&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：我不知道。
Edge allow let? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I don't know.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：有可能。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It might.
我不知道。&gt；&gt；演讲者2：2016年我们都会很好，
I don't know. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We'll all be good in 2016,
因为微软放弃支持
because Microsoft's dropping support
对于所有那些IE浏览器。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我知道你的
for all those IE browsers. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I know your
客户将使用这些浏览器。
customers will be using these browsers.
是啊。微软说我们不支持你
Yeah. Microsoft said we're not supporting you
不再是男人了，但这并不意味着世界将停止使用它。
guys anymore but that doesn't mean that the world's gonna stop using it.
所以，恐怕我们还要在IE上呆上一段时间。
So we're gonna be stuck with IE for a while longer, I'm afraid.
所以全局变量在所有语言中都是邪恶的，它们导致了事物的耦合，
So global variables are evil in all languages they caused coupling of things,
意外碰撞和安全隐患以及各种各样的坏事。
and accidental collisions and security hazards and all sorts of badness.
不幸的是
And unfortunately,
在浏览器中需要使用全局变量，因为没有种类
in the browser the use of global variables is required because there is no kind
允许一个编译单元找到另一个编译单元的链接机制。
of linkage mechanism that allows one compilation unit to find another.
他们只是共享一个共同的全球空间，这是疯狂的。
They just all share a common global space which is crazy.
因此，由于我建议在浏览器应用程序中使用很少全局
So because of that I recommend in browser applications use as few global
变量越多越好，当您这样做时，请将它们全部命名为大写，因为您
variables as possible and when you do, name them all in uppercase because you
希望他们真正脱颖而出，成为危险和重要的东西。
want them to really stand out as something that is dangerous and important.
JavaScript有一个模仿C+和Java新前缀的新前缀。
JavaScript has a new prefix that was modeled after the C++ and Java new prefix.
我不建议永远使用它，但因为它的危险之一是
I don't recommend using it ever but because one of the hazards with it is that
如果您忘记将新的前缀放在构造函数的前面，
if you forget to put the new prefix on the front of a constructor function,
它将重击全局变量，而不是创建新对象。
instead of creating a new object it will clobber global variables.
并且碰巧与您的实例变量具有相同的名称
And happen to have the same names as the instance variables you're
尝试初始化，这很糟糕，而且
trying to initialize which is awful, and
没有运行时警告，没有编译时警告，这太糟糕了。
there's no run time warning no compile time warning it's just awful.
因此，正因为如此，我们在JavaScript中有一个构造函数起作用的约定
So because of that, we have a convention in JavaScript that constructor functions
应使用InitialCaps和
should be named with InitialCaps and
其他任何东西都不能用InitialCaps命名。
nothing else should ever be named with InitialCaps.
这是我们唯一的线索，关于什么需要一个新的前缀和
This is the only clue we have as to what requires a new prefix and
什么不是。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这是
what doesn't. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: This is
JavaScript中允许的东西，但它并不意味着人们期望的东西。
something which is allowed in JavaScript but it doesn't mean what people expect.
所以这种方法似乎与之相关，
So this approach appears to do with it does,
它将创建两个变量a和b，并将它们初始化为0。
it's gonna create two variables a and b and initialize them both to 0.
取而代之的是，它将b初始化为0，然后
What it does instead is, it initializes b to 0 and
创建也变为0的a，但这个不会是本地的
creates a which also become 0, but this one will not be a locally
作用域变量，此变量将是全局变量。
scoped variable, this one will be a global variable.
JavaScript中的一个大设计错误是，如果您没有显式声明
One of the big design errors in JavaScript is, if you do not explicitly declare
函数JavaScript中的变量假设您希望它是
a variable in a function JavaScript assumes that you intended for it to be
一个全局变量，故意这样做是为了让它更容易
a global variable which is something that was done intentionally to make it easier
对于初学者来说，因为他们通常根本不知道变量是什么。
for the beginners because often they didn't know what variables were at all.
但这会让你更难
But it's makes it much harder for
你是因为如果你真的不小心，你的任何变量都可能
you because if you're not really careful, any of your variables could
变成全局变量，在那里它们很容易被踩到。
turn into global variables where they could easily get stepped on.
所以，再一次，推荐你指的是哪一个，然后写出来。
So again, recommend which one of these you mean and write that instead.
用这样的方式写-&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你也可以这样写吗
Write in a way that- &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is it the same way you can
在一个范围上声明多个变量a逗号b逗号c？
declare multiple variables on a range var a comma b comma c?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：b和c是否都成为
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Does b and c all become
全球贵重物品如果你这样做了吗？&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：不，
global valuables if you do that? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No,
在这种情况下你是可以的。
in this kind of form you're okay.
问题是如果你的任务是这样做的话。
The problem is if you assignment to do that.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay,
好吧。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：那么，用一种方式写
okay. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So, write in a way
这清楚地传达了你的意图。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这是另一个
that clearly communicates your intent. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: This is another one
汤普森的，所以b语言是模仿bcpl的，
of Thompson's, so the the b language was modeled after BCPL,
这是一种聪明的小语言。
which was a brilliant little language.
BCPL是第一个大括号语言。
BCPL was the first curly brace language.
BCPL的if语句是正确的，
And BCPL got its if statement right,
条件周围的双亲是可选的。
that the parens around the condition were optional.
结果周围的花括号是必需的。
And the curly braces around the consequence were required.
汤普森颠倒了这一点。
Thompson reversed that.
汤普森让父母满足了条件要求
Thompson made the parents around the condition required and
结果周围的花括号可选。
the curly braces around the consequence optional.
因为这看起来更像Fortran，更符合当时的风格。
Because that looked more like Fortran which was more in the style of the day.
因此，这条语句似乎与这条语句相关，但是
So as result, this statement appears to do with this one does but
实际上这个函数是这样做的，它将无条件地调用c。
actually does with this one does, that it's going to call c unconditionally.
或者阅读声明的人很容易认为c
Or someone reading the statement could easily think that c
只会被有条件地调用，这是一个错误。
is only gonna be called conditionally, that's a bug.
正因为如此，我建议每次都要放上花括号，
And so because of this, I recommend always put the curly braces in every time,
在每一个如果，在每个其他，在每一个时刻，在永远，
on every if, on every else, on every while, on ever for,
每次都把花括号放进去。
every time put the curly braces in.
这只是两个字符，已经完成了。
It's just two characters and it's done.
这样做的成本非常低，它使你的程序更具弹性，
And what that does is for very low cost, it makes your program much more resilient,
这意味着其他人会进来并添加到您的if语句中。
that means that someone else is gonna come in and add to your if statement.
他们将有更大的可能性
They're gonna have a much greater likelihood of being able to do
在没有介绍她的情况下，这是一件非常好的事情，如果你
that without introducing her into it which is a really good thing and if you
如果你把花括号留在外面，你就是在让你的同事失败。
are leaving the curly braces out, you are setting your coworkers up for failure.
这是不可原谅的和不专业的。
Which is inexcusable and unprofessional.
所以总是把它们放进去，我总是收到人们的来信，但是
So always put them in, and I hear from people all the time but
你必须如此努力，这只是两个字符。
you have to go so hard, it's just two characters.
这只是两个糟糕的角色，他们让你的程序变得更好。
It's just two lousy characters and they make your program so much better.
随着我们的过程变得更加敏捷，我们的编码必须更具弹性。
That as our processes become more agile, our coding must be more resilient.
因为我们的程序永远不会结束，对吧？
Cuz our programs are never finished, right?
他们总是处于不断改进的状态
They're always going to be constant states of improvement and
我们需要这样编码。
we need to code that way.
编码我们的程序，使它们更容易随着时间的推移而改进。
Code our programs so that they are more easily improved over time.